The one especially you tell the authority for the name of the day,
and the right of the year.
Item two is the invitation by Pastor First Assembly of God Church,
frame in Brazil.
This frame is here, so it's here.
You know?
Church on it, sir.
It was about a power.
Thank you so much for the bad.
Thank you for that.
That attendance you give us in our city.
That will just rest, rest, rest as meeting
and best our city and state and our country.
That will just match over our service men and women
if they protect us each day.
We're asking for everything.
I need you.
I need to do it by church.
Our point of view is to the flag of the United States of America
and to bring power for which it stands.
One nation, a new god, individual, with the unity and justice for all.
Thanks, Neil.
Thank you.
Item three is public input, non-skeleton question.
The act is in one direction.
The question is to address the authority on the unity and agenda items.
We're being non-identified as a constant agenda.
Staff is recommending the item six to eight for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions on those items, you can obtain the motion.
The motion is to approve there.
And second.
Second.
Go call, please.
Johnson.
All right.
Move it.
High.
All right.
So.
I'm not as new business.
Any new business.
Do you need anything for the trustees?
You know what I mean?
I had one item that.
It's more of a report.
I think the new business.
I think it's better having it under MSUA.
And I'm trying to get over a cold right now.
So, child, please bear with me.
I think I recorded an advance meeting that our emitter, our electrical team, went to Woodward Oklahoma to help with the ice storm.
I don't remember there was a severe ice storm.
Derek Lawler, Kyle Summer, Aunturner and Derek Nolan.
I think most of them were here tonight.
Anyway, they were there for about a couple of weeks.
And during that time, there were about 8,000 meters that were out.
There were 5,000 pounds that were down.
That equates to about 50 to 70 miles of line.
But I believe it was down that they helped with.
And they were four or about 400 linemen that went into that town to help.
And I just wanted to.
But it is as thank them.
And I told them how proud I am.
The city of Miami.
I want to call state to help another city.
And I'm sure there would be people that would come in here to help us.
If they were when that happens to us.
Because we know what's happened in Miami in the past.
And probably one of the features.
So, I responded.
I think it's a little part of that part of the statewide effort to help part of our sister's cities out.
I appreciate.
Guys, we really appreciate our hard work.
And I'm sure the people in Woodward do also.
So, thank you.
Okay.
I didn't attend the staff reports,
supported in your packet and there are staff available
if you have any questions.
There are none.
Any community announcements from trustees?
Next one, Mayor.
I didn't.
Well, it was a gentleman.
I was on the second.
All right.
Just take your paper.
Johnson.
All right.
Lewis.
Aye.